根据你听到的内容，选出相应的图片，并在答题纸上填涂相应的字母代号每个句子念两遍。
1. The little girl enjoys planting flowers in her garden.
The little girl enjoys planting flowers in her garden.
2. Be careful not to get hurt when you play football.
Be careful not to get hurt when you play football.
3. George is always ready to help his classmates solve problems.
George is always ready to help his classmates solve problems.
Direction signs can be useful when you want to find a place.
5. We took part in the dragon boat race last year.
We took part in the dragon boat race last year.
6. My grandpa's singing group will give a performance in the neighborhood.
My grandpa's singing group will give a performance in the neighborhood.
根据你听到的对话和问题，选出最恰当的答案，并在答题纸上填涂相应的字母代号。对话。
7. Hi Jason, are you drawing a cartoon?
No, I'm writing a play.
This is my new hobby.
Question. What is the man's new hobby?
再听一遍。
Hi Jason, are you drawing a cartoon?
No, I'm writing a play.
This is my new hobby.
What is the man's new hobby?
8. David, can you speak Japanese?
Yes, I can.
the 20 shop assistants in our store, six can speak a foreign language.
Question. How many shop assistants in David's store can speak a foreign language?
再听一遍。
David, can you speak Japanese?
Yes, I can.
the 20 shop assistants in our store,
six can speak a foreign language.
Question. How many shop assistants in David's store can speak a foreign language?
9. The trip to the National Park was interesting.
I enjoyed the activities there.
It was boring.
I had been there twice before.
Question. How does the woman like the trip to the National Park?
再听一遍。
The trip to the National Park was interesting.
I enjoyed the activities there.
It was boring.
I had been there twice before.
Question. How does the woman like the trip to the National Park?
10. Is your birthday in April, Jessica?
No, it's on June 2nd.
But this year, I celebrated my birthday on June 1st, Children's Day.
Question. When is Jessica's birthday?
请再听一遍。
Is your birthday in April, Jessica?
No, it's on June 2nd.
But this year, I celebrated my birthday on June 1st, Children's Day.
Question. When is Jessica's birthday?
11. I heard that you moved from the city to the country last year.
Yes. I wanted to live near my office.
Now, it takes me only 10 minutes to get there.
Well, I prefer to live in the city, close to my friends.
Question. Why did the man move to the country?
请再听一遍。
I heard that you moved from the city to the country last year.
Yes. I wanted to live near my office.
Now, it takes me only 10 minutes to get there.
Well, I prefer to live in the city, close to my friends.
Question. Why did the man move to the country?
12. I'm sorry, sir.
Your flight left 15 minutes ago.
Oh, no. I have a lecture to give at 2.30 this afternoon.
What can I do now?
You can go to Gate 5 to change your flight.
The service center is there.
Question. Where is the service center?
请再听一遍。
I'm sorry, sir.
Your flight left 15 minutes ago.
no. I have a lecture to give at 2.30 this afternoon.
What can I do now?
can go to Gate 5 to change your flight.
The service center is there.
Question. Where is the service center?
13. would you like for dinner?
I can cook some noodles or fried chicken.
Well, if you don't mind cooking, noodles sound great.
I like simple food.
Question. What are the two speakers talking about?
再听一遍。
14. would you like for dinner?
can cook some noodles or fried chicken.
Well, if you don't mind cooking, noodles sound great.
I like simple food.
Question. What are the two speakers talking about?
14. Did you stay up last night, Peter?
You look pale.
I'm not feeling well.
I have a headache, Miss Green.
Don't worry. Stay in the classroom and I'll call your mom.
Question. What is the probable relationship between the two speakers?
Did you stay up last night, Peter?
You look pale.
I'm not feeling well.
I have a headache, Miss Green.
Don't worry. Stay in the classroom and I'll call your Question.
What is the probable relationship between the two speakers?
判断句子是否符合你听到的短文内容，符合的用表示，不符合的用表示，并在答题纸上填涂相应的字母代号。短文念两遍：“
do you prefer to see?
A baby panda or a snake?
Most people choose cute animals like pandas.
So cute animals usually get more attention than animals like snakes.
Why don't people like snakes?
The reason is simple.
They're just not cute.
Lucy wants to show people the importance of less cute animals, too.
Who is Lucy?
She is a scientist who studies animals.
Lucy is especially interested in snakes because many of them are in danger of
disappearing and she wants to save them.
Lucy thinks people can find many television shows about cute animals.
So she writes stories on her website about less cute animals like snakes in order to
get people interested in them.
She also makes videos about these animals and puts them online.
People love her fun videos.
Every animal is important in keeping the balance of nature.
If we save snakes, we save other animals, too.
We need to think about the future of all animals and respect all animals.
Every single life matters.
Please Which animal do you prefer to see?
再听一遍。
A baby panda or a snake?
Most people choose cute animals like pandas.
So cute animals usually get more attention than animals like snakes.
Why don't people like snakes?
The reason is simple.
They're just not cute.
Lucy wants to show people the importance of less cute animals, too.
Who is Lucy?
She is a scientist who studies animals.
Lucy is especially interested in snakes because many of them are in danger of
disappearing and she wants to save them.
Lucy thinks people can find many television shows about cute animals.
So she writes stories on her website about less cute animals like snakes in order to
get people interested in them.
She also makes videos about these animals and puts them online.
People love her fun videos.
Every animal is important in keeping the balance of nature.
If we save snakes, we save other animals, too.
We need to think about the future of all animals and respect all animals.
Every single life matters.
D I'm so glad you are finally home,
听对话，用听到的单词完成句子。对话念两遍。
I missed you, Alex.
It's been about one month.
I'm so happy to be back.
look tired, I guess you've had hard days at work, haven't you?
Yes, I have.
is no easy job, but I like to look after patients.
I guess you need to do a lot of things like taking temperatures, visiting patients
regularly, and making sure that they take medicine on time.
Right. Besides, I have other important duties.
You do? Sure.
Today, we had several operations and I cleaned up the emergency room for a few
hours. Sometimes, we have a talk with patients, even their family members, to make
them feel better.
And we tell patients how to work with doctors.
I didn't know that.
I'm proud of you, Mum.
You helped save lives.
How great! Thank you, Alex.
That's so sweet.
Please I'm so glad you are finally home, Mum.
再听一遍。
I missed you, Alex.
It's been about one month.
I'm so happy to be back.
You look tired, Mum.
I guess you've had hard days at work, haven't you?
Yes, I have.
is no easy job, but I like to look after patients.
I guess you need to do a lot of things like taking temperatures, visiting patients
regularly, and making sure that they take medicine on time.
Right. Besides, I have other important duties.
You do? Sure.
Today, we had several operations and I cleaned up the emergency room for a few
hours. Sometimes, we have a talk with patients,
even their family members, to make them feel better.
And we tell patients how to work with doctors.
I didn't know that.
I'm proud of you, Mum.
You helped save lives.
How great! Thank you, Alex.
That's so sweet.
关注公众微信，上海办学，海量资源陪伴升学之路。